Contact

maxim.zorin@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/maximzorin (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Software Development User Interface JavaScript

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)

Maxim Zorin

Lead JavaScript Developer

St Petersburg

Summary

My overall experience of more than 20 years, I have worked at Zodiac Systems, Quest Software (Dell), and JetBrains. My current expertise is in the JavaScript stack. I hold a master's degree in Math and CS from Moscow Pedagogical State University.

I love spending time with my family, also I enjoy traveling, hiking, canoeing, and playing board games.

Experience

Zodiac Systems

Lead JS Developer

September 2019 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Embedded JS dev, web dev, and lead for solutions in Interactive TV, customer demos, internal web portals.

Peter the Great St.Petersburg Polytechnic University JavaScript Teacher October 2014 - June 2018 (3 years 9 months)

St Petersburg, St Petersburg City, Russia Led courses in JavaScript and Nodejs.

Zodiac Interactive

5 years

Head of JS Technologies Department December 2014 - 2018 (4 years)

Managed up to 20 people developer team.

Lead JavaScript Developer
October 2013 - December 2014 (1 year 3 months)

JetBrains Senior UI Developer August 2012 - July 2013 (1 year) Web dev of a new version control system.

Zodiac Interactive

1 year 8 months

Head of UI Department

July 2011 - July 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Senior JavaScript Developer

December 2010 - June 2011 (7 months)

Quest Software

Senior Software Developer

March 2007 - June 2011 (4 years 4 months)

Custom dev Active Roles, JavaScripting ActiveDirectory and Windows.

Quest Software

4 years 10 months

C# Developer

April 2004 - September 2006 (2 years 6 months)

ASP.NET web dev user provisioning, self-service management and security, management ActiveDirectory, recovery Exchange, customize SharePoint.

Head of Quality Assurance

December 2001 - March 2004 (2 years 4 months)

Managed QA dept of Moscow branch of the company.

Novalumen

Lead of Quality Assurance

November 2000 - November 2001 (1 year 1 month)

QA the 1st version of beeline.ru, one of the first interactive websites on the Internet.

Goodwin Management Corporation

Webmaster

October 1999 - November 2000 (1 year 2 months)

Web dev 1st version website of the company.

MPSU

Teacher of mathematics and computer science September 1995 - September 1999 (4 years 1 month)

Education

Moscow Pedagogical State University

Master of Science - MS, Mathematics and Computer Science · (September

1992 - June 1997)

Moscow School 91

Associate of Science (A.S.), Mathematics · (1989 - 1992)